wordexceltemplates.com 2019-03-16

# PRIVACY POLICY | Word & Excel Templates

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Our website collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://wordexceltemplates.com website (“Site”).

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. The non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

## Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. A user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

## How we use collected information

Our website may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:  
– To run and operate our Site  
We may need your information display content on the Site correctly.  
– To personalize user experience  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
– To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. You may learn more about opting out of major ad networks at https://websitebuilders.com/tools/advertiser-opt-out/.

Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non-personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Changes to this privacy policy

Our website has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

This document was last updated on May 31, 2018

Maintaining the privacy of our visitors is our top priority. The information received and used by us is outlined in this privacy policy document.

## Log Files

We make use of log files in order to obtain information about the following:

  * Types of internet browsers used to access the website
  * Internet Service Providers
  * Date and time stamp
  * Exit pages
  * Number of clicks

This information is utilized for the purpose of studying and analyzing the following.

  * The visitor trends
  * Collection of demographic statistic
  * Tracking how a visitor moves around the website.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Cookies are not used to manipulate information about visitor preferences. All user-specific information including the accessed web pages is privacy protected. We do not modify web content based on any information send through internet browsers.

## Double Click Dart Cookie

Cookies and web beacons may be used by our advertising partners to place relevant ads on the website. One of the third-party vendors associated with our website is Google. It serves ads on the site based on the following information.

  * Information received through cookies.
  * Information received through DART cookie which reveals the websites visited by individual visitors when they click on ads or visit an AdSense publisher’s website.

Users may seek privacy protection against DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at this URL: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Our other advertising partners are AdSense and Media.net. The technology used by these ad partners sends ads and links appearing on [www.pedometer-reviews.net](http://www.pedometer-reviews.net/) directly to your browser. This reveals your IP address to them. Other technologies include the use of cookies, web beacons and JavaScript. This enables advertising networks to evaluate how effective their ads are. They may also modify the advertising content based on this information.

Our website plays no role in accessing or controlling the information – including cookies, Dart cookie, and web beacons – manipulated by third-party advertising servers. The privacy policy of our website does not have any control over the practices and activities of these servers. Visitors who wish to protect their privacy against these ad networks should follow the instructions given below.

  * Refer to the individual privacy policies of each of our advertising partners in order to find instructions for protecting your privacy against their practices.
  * You may disable cookies through your browser options.
  * Visit the official website of your particular browser in order to find detailed information about managing cookies.

Details about the privacy policy offered by our website are discussed below.

## What Personal Information do we collect?

We never ask for the visitors personal or bank information. Sometimes the only information we ask for is used to create a database of our website users. Such information includes the email address of our visitors.

## Use of the Collected Information

The personal information of visitors collected by us is used for the following purposes.

  * Informing the clients about our website updates.
  * Updating the users about the current news as well as the on-going trends related to our industry.
  * Responding to queries by sending the answers directly to the provided email address of our users.

Our clients may request to opt out of receiving these updates from us.

## Protection of your Information

All of the collected information about clients is stored in password-protected data files. Access to these files is limited to our employees only through the use of security software. This access is solely for the purpose of maintenance or fulfilling other website related requirements.

## Cookies

A cookie is created whenever a visitor lists our website as a favorite. The purpose of this cookie is to track such clients. This information is neither sold to third-parties nor used for commercial promotions. Only our staff has access to these cookies.

## Google AdSense

Google AdSense advertisements appear on our website from time to time through the use of Google Dart Cookies. This is not due to any personal information manipulated by us. You may read about Google’s policy about their Dart Cookies at this link: <https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>

## Accepting our Privacy Policy Terms & Conditions

We hold the right to make modify our policies at any time. Our clients would be notified immediately about policy updates. These changes are highlighted and are easy to pinpoint by the clients. Our clients are advised to review our policies from time to time in order to stay abreast of such changes. The users and subscribers of our website agree to accept our policies by using the website and its products.

## Contact Us

Any questions about our privacy policy can be asked via email sent through the contact section on our website.

Email: adneyadolfaiken(@)gmail(dot)com
